# Meena Jim George

### **Full-Stack Web Developer**



0481 107 418



meena\_jim@yahoo.com



github.com/meenajim

#### **PROFILE**

I have recently returned to the IT industry after a 10 year career break raising my 2 kids. I used to work as a web developer in a university in Cyprus. I'm passionate about full-stack web development and I love getting along with people from different cultures. My goal is to immerse myself in front end web development and be part of a team that creates immersive web experiences.

#### **EDUCATION**

2018 WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE

General Assembly (GA)

2001-2004 MASTER OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Sikkim Manipal University

1998-2001 BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (CHEMISTRY)

Mahatma Gandhi University

## EXPERTISE

Full-Stack Web Development, Front end development, Github, APIs, Heroku, Nokogiri, Cloudinary, Ruby gems, PostgreSQL.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

2007-2009 European University

**WEB DEVELOPER** 

Administered the University's website and content management system. Worked with several university departments to gather content for the website and performed updates on the various portals of the

university

2004-2005 7CEES Group/Sun Infosys

**TRAINEE** 

Various application were designed and developed using

VB.Net and SQL Server for several companies.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Ruby on Rails, Javascript, JQuery, React.JS, HTML, CSS (Bootstrap), Underscore, AJAX, SQL, Visual Basic.

#### **PROJECTS PERFORMED**

#### **GA Projects**

NutriTracker app (Full stack - Rails, API's, etc.)
Bike Sharing application (Full stack - Rails)
Music School CRUD application (Full stack - Rails)
Tic Tac Toe Game (Javascript)

#### Projects performed as part of degree course

Hospital Management System: (VB application interface

with MS Access Database)

Library Management System: (VB application interface

with Oracle 8i Database)

#### REFERENCES

Available on request